A Guide to the William E. Elmore Papers, 1976-2006
Library of Virginia
- Series VI. Miscellaneous Files., Extent: 2 boxes. (Box 34-35)
  - Miscellany File 5 - The Bolling Family by T. T. Empsall (England). (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Miscellany File 6 - Deaf Children. (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Miscellany File 7 - Will of Robert Kinge, Stafford County (Missing) - see Musselman File. (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Miscellany File 8 - Colonial Homes Letters to the Editor. (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - "Out of Ohio: James Wilson's Other Nine Children" by Lisa Hill. (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Pocahontas Trails Quarterly 1985-1990. (Box 34, Folder 23-25)
  - Pocahontas Trails Quarterly 1991-1993. (Box 35, Folder 1-3)
  - Pocahontas Quarterly 1995. (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Postage and Data Entry Reports. (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Reference - Ancestor Index to Bolling Family Directory by Dorothy J. McKinley - Compiled by Norma Bowling Paqualino. (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Reference - Family History Library Books. (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Reynolds, Stacy J. (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Spin Off Lines - Fleming. (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Wilson/Bolling. (Box 35, Folder 10)